Sam Gejdenson Papers 2001.0008
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, undated, 1966-2001
  - Speeches, Press Releases, and Mailings, undated, 1981-1984 (Box 93)
    - Middletown "Dear Friend" letter, 1981 September 7
    - Old Press Releases, 1980-1981
    - Record Statement on the Budget, 1981 April 27
    - The Day Bill, 1981
    - Warren B. Richardson, 1981
    - GAO Report: Territory Recovery Program, 1981
    - Pratt & Whitney, Conrail Transfer, 1981
    - Navy Boycott of Electric Boat, 1981
    - Airborne Warning and Control System (AWACS)/ F-15, 1981
    - Infant Formula, 1981 May 27
    - Death of Cardinal Wyzynoki, 1981 June 1
    - "Reflections of a Child of the Holocaust", 1981 June 21
    - Voting Records, 1981
    - Interior Assignment, 1981 February 2
    - Withdrawal of Richardson, 1981 April 15, 23
    - Stop AWAC Sale, 1981 April 23
    - Statement before Labor Committee, 1981 June 16
    - Firefighters' Day, 1981 June 11
    - Republican Relist, 1981 June
    - Discipline of the Democrats, 1981 July 1
    - Tax Cut Legislation, 1981 July 21
    - Udall Tax Subsidy, 1981 July 29
    - Gejdenson is a Target, 1981 July 21
    - Cotter's Death, 1981 September 8
    - Mailgram, 1981 September 23
    - Seapower Testimony, 1981 September 23
    - John Rose, 1981 September 23
    - Hadassah Meeting, 1981 September 14
    - Dairy Prices, 1981 October 1
    - Cron Falashas, 1981 Novermber 6
    - Testimony on Coast Guard, 1982 January 29
    - Romantic Willimantic, 1982 Febuary 14
    - Letter to Reagan Requesting a Meeting, 1982 Feburary 11
    - Friends of Ireland, 1982 Feburary 7
    - Holocaust Survivors, 1982 June 16
    - CR Indian Land Claim Bill, 1982 June 16
    - Freeze Statement, 1982 August 5
    - Troops in Lebanon, undated
    - Disaster Assistance, 1982 March 2
    - Speeches, 1981-1982
    - Letters to Newspapers, 1981-1983
  - Recorded Votes, Gejdenson's Voting Record, Legislation, 1981-2000 (Box 94)
    - Recorded Votes, 97th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 1981-1982
    - Recorded Votes, 98th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 1983-1984
    - Recorded Votes, 99th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 1985-1986
    - Recored Votes, 100th Congress, 1st Session, 1987
    - Recorded Votes, 102nd Congress, 1st session, 1991
    - Gejdenson's Foreign Policy Record, 1981-2000
    - Foreign Policy Legislation, 1997-1998
    - Defense Legislation, 1997-1999
  - Co-signed, Press Clippings, Legislation, Boater Guide, undated, 1996-2000 (Box 95)
    - Co-signed Legislation and Co-signed Letters, 105th and 106th Congresses, undated, 1996-2000
    - United States' Code, 2000
    - Press Clippings, 1998-2000
    - Dear Colleague Letters and other Correspondence, 106th Congress, 1999-2000
    - Connecticut Boater's Guide, 2000
  - Environment and General Bills, undated, 1993-1996 (Box 96)
    - Environmental Scorecards, undated, 1993-1996
    - Attack Reports, 1995-1996
    - Mystic Seaport, 1993-1995
    - Public Marketing Adminstraration, 1996 September 19
    - Long Island Sound Information, 1996
    - Onmi-Touch, Mystic, undated, 1993-1995
    - Democratic Policy Committee Reports, 1995
    - Fisheries Subcommittee, 1995
    - House Resolution 1112, 1995 May 6
    - Young Territories Bill, 1995
    - Democratic Caucus Rules, 103rd and 104th Congresses, 1993, 1995
    - Native American Recognition Bill, 1994-1995
    - Marine Research, 1996 January
    - Hirshon Case, 1995
    - Crocker Boat Yard, 1995
    - Millstone Fish Hatchery, 1996
    - Lieberman Trust Bill, 1995
    - Resource Committee, 1996
    - Water Resource Development Act, 1996
    - Norwich Harbor Project, 1994-1996
    - Safe Drinking Water Act, 1996
    - Atlantic Point, 1994-1996
    - Mystic River Rock, 1994-1996
    - NVRP, 1996
    - Ocean Base I, 1995
    - Wetlands Reserve Program, 1994
    - Umatilla Bill, 1994-1996
    - Vernon Brownfield Initiative, 1996
    - House Resolution 1675, 1994-1996
    - Layard Wildlife, 1994-1996
    - Environment, 2000
  - Sponsored Legislation, Gejdenson's Voting Record, Gejdenson's Accomplishments, Miscelleanous Legislation, Undated 1981-1994 (Box 97)
    - Toy Bill, 1988-1990
    - Environment Tax, 1990 March 5
    - Gejdenson's Sponsored Legislation, 97th- 101st Congresses, 1981-1989
    - Gejdenson's Accomplishments, 102nd Congress, 1991-1992
    - Co-signed Letters: Foreign Affairs, 1987-1988
    - Sponsored and Co-Sponsored Bills, 1989
    - Legislative Activity Guide, 103rd Congress, 1st session, January- June, 1994
    - Gejdenson's Legislative Profile, 1993 June 5- 1994 June 30
    - Member's Voting Record, 97th-98th Congresses, 1981-1984
    - Legislative Profile, 1991-1992
    - Democratic Study Group, Recorded Voted, 100th Congress, 2nd Session, 101st Congress, 1988-1990
  - Tourism and Education, undated, 1988-2000 (Box 98)
    - Wildlife and Fisheries, 1988
    - Connecticut Tourism Impact Studies, 1988-1999
    - Education "Growth", 1998-1999
    - Vacation Guides and Brochures, 1994-1999
    - Eastern Connecticut Tourism, 1996-2000
    - Tourism, 1995-1998
    - Tourism Reports, 1990-1997
    - Tourism Report Research, 1997-1998
    - Tourism Colloquy, 1994 May 11
  - Impeachment, 1998 (Box 99)
    - Supplemental Materials to the Referral of the United States' House of Representatives, Submitted by the Office of the Independent Council, 1998 September 9
    - Appendicies to the Referral of the United States' House of Representatives, Submitted by the Office of the Independent Council, 1998 September 9
  - Daily Schedule, 1987 October 1- 1992 December 3 (Box 100)
    - Gejdenson's Daily Schedule, 1987 October 1- 1992 December 3
  - Legislation Issues, Mailings, and District Events, Bulk, 1990-2000; undated, 1966, 1990-2000 (Box 101)
    - Cereal, 1995-1997
    - Social Security, 1996
    - Service Men Mailing, 2000
    - Arthur Lanbury, 1999-2000
    - Just For Seniors: Deceptive Mailings, 1999
    - Fraud Conference, 1994-1996
    - Scanner Bill, 1994-1997
    - BIF-SAIF, 1995-1996
    - Banking, 1992-1996
    - Securities Reform, 1994-1995
    - Congressional Immunity, 1994
    - House Oversight Committee, 1995-1998
    - Ethics Reform, undated
    - Federal Pay, 1990-1991
    - House Resolution 3700, 1996
    - Reportations, 1996
    - Repeal of the 9 Term Act, 1966, 1996
    - Massachusetts Recount, 1994-1996
    - Lobbying Reform, 1995
    - Congressional Pensions, 1995-1996
    - Congressional Travel Policy, 1998
    - Contested Elections, 1998
  - Records, Legislative Activity, Co-signed bills and letters, Talking Points, undated, 1975-1998 (Box 102)
    - Co-sponsored Bills, 1996-1998
    - Co-signed Letters, 1987-1988, 1991, 1996-1998
    - Co-signed Bills and Letters, 1995
    - "Extension of Remarks,", 1981-1994
    - Congressional Record, 97th-103rd Congresses, 1981-1994
    - Court Case, 1987-1992
    - Talking Points and Memos, undated, 1995-1998
    - Legislative Activity Guide, 105th Congress, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 1997-1998
    - Legislative Record Index, Connecticut State Legislature, 1975-1978
    - Magazine Index, 1988
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1996-1998 (Box 103)
    - Press Clips, Press Releases, undated, 1997-1998
    - Senior Fraud Conference, 1996 April 24
    - Norwich Bulletin, undated,1995-1996
    - Finance/Schedule, undated, 1996-1998
    - Current Issues, undated
    - Op/Eds, undated, 1997-1998
    - Surveys, undated, 1998
    - Releases, 1997-1998
    - General Press Clips, undated, 1996-1998
    - "Living Room" Pension Event, 1996 October 24
    - Retirement/Pension, 1997-1998
    - Foreign Policy/Jewish Issues, 1998
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1995 (Box 104)
    - Politics, undated, 1991-1995
    - Connecticut Politics, undated, 1992-1995
    - Journal Inquirer Op/Eds, undated, 1992-1995
    - Middletown Press, undated, 1992-1995
    - Washington Post, undated, 1992
    - USA Today, 1992
    - Willimantic Chronicle, undated, 1992-1995
    - State of the Union, undated, 1995
    - Hartford Courant, undated, 1991-1995
    - New London Day, undated, 1994-1995
    - Norwich Bulletin, undated, 1992-1995
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1993
    - Mashantuckets, undated, 1993-1995
    - Casino/Gambling, undated, 1993-1995
    - Pequots, undated, 1994-1995
    - Native Americans, undated, 1993-1994
    - Pequots and Land, undated, 1993
  - Education, undated, 1990-2000 (Box 105)
    - College Afforability Roundtable, 1997-1998
    - Connecticut State University, 1999
    - Fairfield University, 1998-2000
    - Direct Loans, 1993-1998
    - Connecticut College, 2000
    - Individuals with Disabilities Education Act, House Resolution 2336, 1990-1993
    - Connecticut Community College, 1994
    - Javits, Gifted and Talented Research Center, 1993, 1996
    - Middlesex Student Loan Defult, 1997-2000
    - Student Federal Aid: Connecticut Colleges, 1996-1999
    - Student Loan Default, 1991-1997
    - Connecticut Student Loan Fund, 1991-1999
    - Conference, Education, 1997
    - University of Bridgeport, 1998
    - TRIO, 1993-2000
    - University of Connecticut's Appropriations, 1997-2000
    - Lifetime Learning, 1994-1999
    - Principals, Email lists, undated, 1999
    - Employeer Education Tax, 1993-1999
    - Amendment, Juvenilles, 1999
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, College Retirement Equities Fund, TIAA-CREF, 1996-1997
    - Jobs Training Program, 1993-1994
    - Federal Direct Loan Information, 1997
    - Clinton's Tax Breaks for College, 1996
  - Legislative Profiles and Legislative Activity Guides, 1989-1994 (Box 106)
    - Gejdenson's Legislative Profiles, 1989 January 3 - 1990 December 11, 1993 January 5 - 1993 December 31
    - Legislative Activity Guides, 102nd Congress, 2nd Session, 103rd Congrees, 1st and 2nd Sessions, 1992-1994
  - Agriculture, undated, 1985-1992 (Box 107)
    - Agriculture Press, undated, 1990
    - 42 and Strike Capland, 1991
    - Desalinization, 1991
    - California Drought, 1989-1992
    - CVP, 1992
    - Double Subsidy Report, Dissent, 1991
    - House Resolution 429, Surplus Crops, 1991
    - D.S. Committee, 1991
    - Cotton Program, 1989-1990
    - Endorsements, 1990
    - Irrigation Subsidy, 1985-1988
    - Water Article, 1991
    - Garrison Diversion, 1986
    - Drought, Dear Colleague Letters, 1991
    - Drought, Gejdenson's Statement, 1991 April 20
    - Acerage Limitation, 1989-1991
    - Amendment, House Resolution 429, 1991
    - Columbia Basin, 1989-1991
    - State by State, undated
    - Community, 1989
    - D.S. Handout, 1987-1990
    - Dear Colleague Letters and Other Correspondence, 1989-1991
    - Payment Cap, 1985-1990
    - House Resolution 1443, 1987-1989
  - Daily Schedules, Flags Flown over Capital, Contact Lists, undated, 1984-1999 (Box 108)
    - Tours of the Capital and Flags Flown over Capital, undated, 1992
    - Contacts, undated
    - Gejdenson's Daily Schedule, 1997 July 18 to 1998 December 13
    - Gejdenson's Daily Schedule, 1984 January 13 to 1987 October 1
    - Gejdenson's Daily Schedule, undated, 1999
  - Constitution, Jefferson's Manuals, Rules and Practices of the House of Representatives, Hearings, undated, 1981-1983, 1989-1999 (Box 109)
    - Constitution and Jefferson's Manual,101st Congress, 104th - 105th Congresses, 1989-1990, 1995-1999
    - Rules and Practices of the House od Representatives, 97th Congress, 101st Congress, 104th -105th Congresses, 1981-1983, 1989-1991, 1995-1999
    - Hearings, Background, and Mark-Up Materials, Volumes 1-4, 103rd Congress, 1st Session, 1993
  - Education Conference, General Education Files, undated, 1995-2000 (Box 110)
    - E-newletters, 1999-2000
    - General Education, 2000 March 4
    - History, 1999-2000
    - "Leading Edge,", 2000
    - Science and Technology, 2000
    - Special Education, 2000
    - Press Clips of the Conference, 2000
    - Logistics, 2000
    - Photographs, 2000
    - Pre-planning for the Conference, 1998-2000
    - Net-Tech, Block Trust, 1999-2000
    - Program for the Conference, 2000
    - Registration, 2000
    - Teacher Training Questions, 1999
    - Evaluations from the Conference, 2000
    - Commerce Meeting, Notes, undated, 2000
    - Gejdenson's School Visits, 1997-1999
    - Gejdenson Press Clips, undated, 1995
    - Coventry School Roundtable, 1999
    - Middletown High School E-rate, undated
    - Eastern Schools, 1999 September 7
    - After-school Programs, Killingly, 1997-1999
    - After-school Program, Middletown, 1999 April 13
    - Norwich Tech Event, 1999
    - Stonington School Kick-off Community Coalition, 1999
    - After-School Program, Norwich, 1999 28 Feburary, 2000
    - Online Town Meeting, 2000 September 19
    - Grants, 21st Century, 1999-2000
  - School Technology, undated, 1997-2000 (Box 111)
    - E-rate Complaints, undated, 1999
    - Education and Technology Roundtable, 1998
    - E-rates, Connecticut, 1999
    - USF-E-rates, 1997-1999
    - E-rate, Year 1, Waves 1-8, undated, 1998-1999
    - E-rate, Year 2, Waves 1-20, undated, 1999
    - E-rate, Year 3, Waves 1-23, undated, 2000
    - E-Rate, County, 1999
    - School Technology, 1997-1998
    - Education and Technology, New England Schools, Vernon, 1997
    - Peronal Computers in Space, 1997
    - Computer Donations, 1997
    - Education and Technology Conference, 1998
    - School/Business Technology Partners, 1997
    - School Technology Assesment Survey, 1997
    - E-rate Videocassette, 1998
  - Defense Files, undated, 1981-1995 (Box 112)
    - Technology in Connecticut, undated, 1992-1993
    - Electric Boat Conversion, 1986-1992
    - Submarine Base, 1993-1995
    - Sage-Allen, 1993
    - Why Gejdenson Missed Votes, 1981-1994
    - Defense Correspondence, 1991-1992
    - Robo Letters, undated
    - Base Closure and Realignment Commission (BRAC), Navy Base Closure Recommendations, 1993
    - SOSES, 1993
    - Ocean Thermal Energy Conservation, 1993
    - Sea Worthy, 1993-1994
    - Defense Finance and Accounting Service, Southbridge, 1992-1994
    - Connecticut Diversification, 1992
    - Defense Conversion, 1992-1995
    - Defense Conversion Committee, 1989-1993
  - Defense Files, Correspondence and Distict Events, undated, 1981-1993 (Box 113)
    - Diversification, 1993 August
    - Temporary Resident Permit, Connecticut, 1993
    - Labor and Diversity Conference, 1993
    - Submarine Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1993
    - Press Releases, undated, 1980-1981, 1983-1985
    - Special Reports, 1983-1985
    - Robo Letters, 1981-1984
    - Statements, Special Reports, Campaign Release, and Newsletters, 1981-1982
  - Foreign Affairs, Iran-Contra, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 114)
    - The Bernsteins, 1986
    - Phillippines, Investigation, undated, 1982-1986
    - Elliott Abrams, 1987
    - Ross Letter, 1987 June 17
    - Government Accountibility Office and Congressional Research Service Reports, 1984-1987
    - Guatemala, 1988 March
    - Honduran Missile Excerises, 1984-1987
    - $27 Million, Where?, 1987
    - Robowen, undated, 1985-1986
    - Contra Funding, 1985-1986
    - Contra Aid, 1988
    - Contra History, undated, 1987
    - Dowling, 1985-1987
    - Human Rights Reports, 1985-1987
    - Biographies and Stories, undated, 1982-1985
    - Press Clippings, 1984-1985
    - House Foreign Affairs Committee and Iran-Contra, 1986-1987
    - Iran-Contra, undated, 1987
    - Central Intelligence Agency: Report on Brody, 1985-1986
    - Notes and Memos, undated, 1984-1985
    - Drug Trafficking, 1985-1986
    - World Population Count, 1985
    - Central America, 1986-1987
    - Foreign Policy, 1985-1987
  - Videocassettes, undated, 1984-1990 (Box 115)
    - Unlabeled (7), 1986
    - Unlabeled (2), undated
    - Contra (2), 1985, 1987
    - Debates and Testimony (2), 1984, 1989
    - Public Broadcasting Service (1), 1990
    - "Ask Congress" (1), 1986 April 13
    - "Crossfire" (1), 1986 February11
    - Foreign Policy (4), 1985-1989
    - Native Americans (2), undated, 1986
    - Diversification (1), 1990 September 18
    - Gejdenson's Videocassette (1), 1984
    - Unidentified (4), 1985, 1989
    - ABC News "Nightline" (1), 1990 February 8
    - C-SPAN (1), 1990 March 23
  - Defense Files, Legislative Record and Mailings, undated, 1977, 1981-1995 (Box 116)
    - Defense Conversion, 1990-1995
    - Diversification, 1991-1992
    - Aspin-Frost, Diversification, Fiscal Year 1993, 1991
    - United Technologies, Autoturbines, 1993-1994
    - Newletters, undated, 1981-1990
    - Mailings, General, undated, 1984-1994
    - "Updates,", undated, 1983-1985
    - Seniors and Health Mailings, undated, 1984-1985
    - "Dear Friends" Letters, undated, 1989
    - Conference Brochures, undated, 1984-1990
    - Jim Wright, Ethics, Bulk, 1988-1989; 1977, 1988-1989
    - Letters to Constituents, undated, 1986-1989
    - Co-signed Letters, undated, 1989-1990
  - House Journal, undated, 1980-1989 (Box 117)
    - 96th Congress, 2nd Session, Part 2, 1980
    - 99th Congress, 2nd Session, Part 1, 1986
    - 100th Congress, 1st Session, Part 2, 1987
    - 100st Congress, 2nd Session, Part 1 and Part 2, 1988
    - 101st, 1st Session, Part 1, 1989
  - Defense and Military Files, undated, 1975-1990 (Box 118)
    - Griffin, Lawsuit, undated, 1975-1989
    - Briggs, undated, 1988-1989
    - Byrzak Case, 1984-1985
    - Eva Jones, 1989-1990
    - Eagan/Doane, 1989
    - Defense Contractor Problems, 1986-1988
    - Department of Defense Contracting, 1984-1986
    - "Revolving Door" Ethics Hearing, 1987-1988
    - Zygo, 1987
    - Plastics Intervention Molding, 1988
    - House Resolution 2720, 1988-1990
    - Prisoners of War and Soldiers Missing in Action Medal, POWs/MIAs Medal, 1984-1985
    - G.I. Bill, 1985
    - G.I. Bill, Connecticut, 1982-1985
    - Veterans' Health Bill, 1985
    - Veterans' Benefits, 49th Division, 1985
    - Turn-Around Cruise, undated, 1985-1989
    - Merchant Marines, 1987-1988
    - Navy, Health Care, 1985-1987
    - Submarine Base Clinics, 1986-1987
    - Compensation Benefits, Veterans, 1987-1988
    - Veterans' Center, Norwich, 1985-1988
    - Vietnam Veteran, Ed Benes, 1985-1989
    - Veterans Adminstration, Disability Compensation, 1988
    - Veterans Budget, 1987-1988
    - Dear Colleague Letters, undated, 1987-1988
    - Veterans' Center Notes, undated, 1985
    - Military and Retired Military, Connecticut Issues, 1984-1985
    - Connecticut Veterans, 1988-1989
    - Veterans' Issues, 1985-1989
    - Judicial Review, 1986-1989
    - Veterans' Hospitals, Changes, 1989
    - Veterans Association, Health Benefits, 1986-1988
    - Veterans' Center, Correspondence, 1984
    - Veterans' Status, American Airlines, 1989
    - Veterans' Center, Press Releases and Press Clippings, undated, 1984-1985
    - Veterans Association Hospital, Budget Shortfalls, 1988-1989
    - Veterans Small Business Conference, 1988
    - Jewish Veterans, 1989
    - Veterans' Training, undated
  - Press Clippings, Press Releases, Photographs, and Events, undated, 1989-1994 (Box 119)
    - Defense Press, undated, 1989-1993
    - Photographs, undated
    - Diversification Clips, undated, 1989-1992
    - Simon Wiesenthal Center Dinner, Guest List, Program, undated, 1989
    - Election 1994, undated, 1994
    - Recount, undated, 1994 November - December
    - Campaign 1994, undated, 1993-1994
    - Jewish Programs, undated, 1993-1994
    - Manshantucket Pequots, undated, 1993
    - Mohegans, undated, 1993
    - Diversification Press and Information Packet, undated, 1989
    - Press Releases, undated, 1989-1990
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1996 (Box 120)
    - Clips of Gejdenson, undated, 1994-1996
    - Seawolf, undated, 1995-1996
    - Submarine Base, undated, 1995-1996
    - Taxes, undated, 1996
    - Tourism, undated, 1995-1996
    - Transportation, undated, 1995-1996
    - University of Connecticut, undated, 1995-1996
    - Veterans, undated, 1995-1996
    - Waste/Energy, undated, 1995-1996
    - Hartford Courant Op/Ed, Undated, 1995-1996
    - Welfare, undated, 1995-1996
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1996
    - Willimantic Chronicle Op/Eds, undated, 1995-1996
    - Journal Inquirer Op/Eds, undated, 1995-1996
    - Unidentfied Op/Eds, undated, 1992-1996
    - New London Day Op/Eds, undated, 1995-1996
    - Presidential Election, undated, 1996
  - Defense Files, Press Releases, Correspondence, undated, 1981-1989 (Box 121)
    - Defense Spending, 1990
    - Diversification, Prepared Statistics, 1984-1985
    - Diversification, Graduate Student Resources, 1985-1988
    - Economic Development, undated, 1988-1989
    - House Resolution 4698, 1984-1986
    - House Resolution 277, 1987-1988
    - Defense Dependency Study, 1980
    - Department of Defense Adjustment, 1983-1987
    - Diversification, Economic Development Administration, 1986-1989
    - Robo Letters, undated, 1981-1987
    - Press Releases, undated, 1984-1987
  - Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) and Press Releases, undated, 1984-1989 (Box 122)
    - National Vietnam Veterans Readjustment Study, 1988
    - Veterans' Health, 1984-1988
    - Post Truamatic Stress Disorder (PTDS) Studies, undated, 1985-1987
    - Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD), 1984-1988
    - Brief on New Bill, 1989
    - Senate Oversight Hearing, Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD), 1989 June 14
    - Geographic Information on Veterans' Hospitals, undated
    - PTSD Quarterly, 1987-1988
    - Post Truamatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) Center in New Haven, 1989
    - Inquiries, 1988-1989
    - William Ryiz, 1988
    - General files, 1988
    - National Vietnam Veterans' Readjustment Study, 1988
    - Co-Sponsors, 1988
    - Record Statement, 1988
    - Dear Colleague Letters, 1988
    - Press Clippings, 1988
    - Bill Draft, 1988
    - Power Hearings, 1987 July 1
    - George's Bank, 1987 February 2
    - Roberts' Response, 1987 June 19
    - Remove Roberts, 1987 June 17
    - Women's Veteran's Memorial, 1987 November 10
    - Portland Hearing, 1987 November 6
    - Sheena Ducan, South Africa, 1987November 4
    - Indian Artifact Hearing, 1987 October 16
    - Persian Gulf, 1987 October 19
    - Electric Bill Passes, 1987 October 27
    - Low Income Energy, 1987 November 2
    - McKinney Special Order, 1987 May 29
    - F-5 Hearings, 1987 May 19
    - Arts Contest, 1987 May 20
    - Dowling, Fake Priest, 1987 June 3
    - U.S.- Canada Interparlimentary Group, 1987 June 4
    - Home Base Business, 1987 April
    - Town Meetings, 1987 March 7
    - Longshoremen Case, 1987
    - Veterans, 1987-1988
    - Taxes, 1987
    - Newsletter, 1987 Spring
    - Tax Seminar, 1987 January 29
    - Seatech, 1987 October 9
    - Workshop, Procument of Immigration, 1987 October 7
    - Statement on Markey Seabrook Amendment, 1987 August 4
    - Surgeon General's AIDS Report, 1987 August 28
    - Letters to Veterans Affairs regarding Linda Schwarz, undated
    - Academy Nominations, 1987 October 5
    - Price-Anderson Bill Passes, 1987 July 30
    - Depo-Prevera Hearings, 1987 July 30
    - Backfit Advances, 1987 October 9
    - Volunteer Awards, 1987 July 26
    - Advance Tongass, 1987 May 18
    - Military Construction (MILCON) Appropriations, 1987 July 14
    - Letter on Drug Rule, 1987 July 1987
  - Press Clippings, Press Releases, undated, 1985-2000 (Box 123)
    - Newletters, 1989-1991
    - Press Hits on Gejdenson, undated, 1991
    - Gejdenson Featured in Press, undated, 1989
    - Budget Statement, 1991
    - Naval Undersea Systems Center/Base Closure, undated, 1991
    - Military Construction (MILCON), undated, 1991-1992
    - UNC Naval Products, undated, 1990-1991
    - Soviet Resolutions, 1991
    - Trade, undated, 1991
    - Military, undated, 1990-1991
    - Committees, 1990
    - Foreign Policy, undated, 1991
    - Labor, undated, 1990
    - Electric Boat, Seawolf, undated, 1991